<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' standalone='yes' ?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
  <title>Kakutai</title>
  <link href='https://enceris.github.io/p/'/>
    <link href='https://enceris.github.io/p/atom.xml' rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' />
    <updated>2023-08-24T02:25:51+05:30</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Kakutai</name>
  </author>
  <generator>nue</generator>
  <id>https://enceris.github.io/p/</id>

  <entry>
      <title>Kakutai</title>
      <link rel='alternate' href='https://enceris.github.io/p/2'/>
        <id>https://enceris.github.io/p/2</id>
        <published>1970-01-01T05:30:02+05:30</published>
        <updated>1970-01-01T05:30:02+05:30</updated>
        <summary>	THE REFORMER</summary>
        <a href='/p/2' class='bold'>	A Reflection of War</a>
        <content type='html'><p>--&gt;</p>
<p><em>Babylon's Hell, the area that surrounds Cathedral Hall. The
center itself is part of the plains, which extended to encompass the
northern zone. Master Darus is just north of the hall. East of these
plains is an elevated area with a small lake atop, this is where Theros
stood his ground. These hills grew lower further south, and two rivers
extended from this lake down the hills. One drifted west of the hill
slowly arching southward; the other river continued south before
depositing into a deep valley and ravine. From the river into the lake
is a small waterfall, but the lake continued rushing downward deeper
into the valley; a massive and deceptively beautiful waterfall, which
poured into the domain of one of the most dangerous specters: Chastes, a
warlord-class threat. It appears to take the form of the water itself,
but I have seen how terrifying it truly is. Any being that steps foot in
those waters, they'll continue to get sucked into the current until they
are absorbed. West of this is a great forest, with various elevations,
trees, and creatures. Further north is where Kevin is, and even further
north is where the forest grows thicker. I have seen some of us
reconvene up north, perhaps to prepare for a fight with Kevin or Darus?
Nevertheless, despite the circumstances, Babylon's Hell is a visually
stunning location.</em></p>
<p><em>However, within moments... Babylon's Hell began to live up to its
name, as it descended into something straight out of a nightmare. I had
accounted for each of us to have a unique arsenal of abilities, but it
never crossed my mind that such destruction could happen in such a small
amount of time. The spectral beasts wreaked havoc on our numbers,
chasing the weaker fighters as they fled behind the stronger ones. As
the sky grew orange and black, and the temperatures began rising, the
forest I was once in could barely be called habitable. The lower half
was engulfed in flames; as the ash settled on the ground, it was clear
that even this inferno wasn't enough to provoke Kevin out of his
position. Kevin was considered the strongest, but the other captains are
no joke either; the sound of Theros' shots could be heard from anywhere.
Fire, falling trees, the sickening air, and the occasional knife or
arrow could not even make him flinch. A few warriors charged in to
strike him, yet the force of his parry sent them flying, either
incapacitated from hitting a tree or with a newfound fear of death as
they ran out of the forest. Surprisingly, Master Darus saw the least
challengers. He was out in the open, meaning there was no possibility
for a surprise attack---and he was impervious to ranged attacks as well.
Master Darus was unique in that he had an equal spread of affinity
throughout all four of the human psyche, making him proficient with each
element. Though I wouldn't have imagined he would be able to make such a
powerful barrier around himself.</em></p>
<p><em>The biggest nightmare of all is that some of the specters have
taken the form of other Aesir. These are unique specters, in that they
are more intelligent than they are destructive. They test the traps laid
by us, and even make some of their own. They work together to corner and
torment us, and I have caught wind of a potential hierarchy system among
them. For the sake of being safe, I've stolen three ID cards on my way
out of the forest, moving east towards the lake. I see people
challenging Babel by the river, and he seems to be the best match for
me; perhaps I should take this opportunity?</em></p>
<p>"Above me, state your name."</p>
<p><em>Below? No, to my right. Beneath the overhang, someone is hanging
by the wall? A hideout? Does the cliff cave inward?</em> "Walter du
Aesir. I am no threat."</p>
<p>"Leave this gorge. It's suicide, it ain't worth it."</p>
<p><em>His tone of voice is stern but lacks direction. His judgement is
clouded with fear.</em> "What have you seen?"</p>
<p>"The lake is alive. Babel and Theros are cooperating; before you can
even strike Babel you get downed by Theros. I don't even know if they're
aware how dangerous being sent into the lake is. The lake... it doesn't
let you go."</p>
<p>"Chastes?"</p>
<p>"Not just Chastes, the outskirts of the gorge have a ton of monsters
that look just like us. They fool us, then throw us in when we least
expect it. If I stay here the entire time, I won't be found... and I
won't die. I'll at least live to the end so I can find out why... this
has happened to us. Why have our idols sent us to our death?"</p>
<p><em>Confusion. Fear. Bitterness. He's impaired by these emotions. I
don't blame him. I know that not everybody is as motivated as I am. But
perhaps I may be able to move these people... am I getting closer to the
meaning of honor and glory?</em></p>
<p>"Your name, what is it?"</p>
<p>He scoffed. "What, you wanna remember me when I'm gone? You've got
the presence of a fighter, I'm sure you'll make it outta here. Or maybe
you wanna hold onto a name at your deathbed? Better save that for your
loved ones."</p>
<p>"I stated my name, and I am not a threat. It's common courtesy to
give your own." <em>Perhaps, this shift in tone will benefit me.</em>
"Would you rather I be a threat?"</p>
<p>A short pause. "You've got guts, even if you sound young. A bright
future, huh. The name's Adel."</p>
<p>"Adel du Aesir?"</p>
<p>"Hah, 'course not. We've all had our own lives before becoming an
Aesir. Adel Ewan, that's how I want you to remember me."</p>
<p>"I won't need to be doing any remembering. You're going to survive
this."</p>
<p>"Really? How are you so sure of it, haven't you seen your comrades
die? What makes me any different?"</p>
<p>Walter gently grazed the dirt, the ground beginning to shift. Adel
was slowly raised to the same level as Walter, and within a moment of
seeing his face, Adel had come to realize who he was speaking with.
Walter du Aesir, a prodigy who was born and raised by the Vanir family,
trained by Cassius and Darus. He had always thought that such a man
would never bother with the common folk, for Adel was an average warrior
that sought to protect his family in a small village. Now that he had
matched a voice to an appearance, seeing that fire in Walter's eyes had
resurfaced memories of his own past. His will was reignited once more,
as the days of being a single father taking care of his two children
after his wife's passing. His inability to protect them, and his anguish
and grief quelling his desire to preserve. When he enlisted to join the
imperial guard, his dedication and will had steered him to the path of
an Aesir. Yet as the years passed, his resolve began to dull. Before him
now was something that reinvigorated the scent of his past convictions,
as he saw Walter's eyes burning with determination, calculation,
confidence, and excitement. It was the kind that was pure, untouched,
and unfaltering. They looked at each other for a brief moment, until he
spoke the words that would change Adel's fate.</p>
<p>"Take my hand or follow my lead, and you too will be sure of it."</p>
<hr />
<p><em>Adel's equipment has a lot of use, he must have a lot of
experience in underhanded methods. He has many poisons at his disposal,
and his blades are serrated with chemicals to make each slice more
lethal. Perhaps they are intentionally dulled for this as well.</em></p>
<p><em>We continued to observe Babel as he fought the others. Babel's
very adept with martial arts, and I have yet to see him use his weapon.
Perhaps this is something I have inherited from Darus, but the captains
often keep their weapon unsheathed the same way I do. Perhaps they await
the true challenge, are they observing us keenly?</em></p>
<p><em>At some point, it was far too dangerous to remain by the gorge.
The specters grew in numbers and strength, and it became difficult for
Adel to determine who was friend or foe. They behaved just like us, and
they didn't harm us immediately. They were accruing information on us...
we should remain on the low. For the time being, I fortified the
entrance of a cave so that we may stay here.</em></p>
<p>"Adel, what does honor and glory mean to you?"</p>
<p>"Are you talking about Her Majesty's words? I had a feeling they were
important, but it just ain't possible to think about it in this
madness."</p>
<p>"Madness... is an understatement."</p>
<p><em>This isn't a trial or our deaths. It's much worse. These specters
are unique, and the fact that Cassius has not intervened means all of
this is intentional. They disguise themselves as us, win us over and
betray us. We are not only cast to our deaths, but we have to decide
whether or not to slay each other as well. Fear overcomes us, taking the
lives of one another is the safest choice. With the deceptive beasts out
there, we have more than enough reason to cut down one of our own. Given
this, the fear building within us wants to fool our minds. I... must
mend it to my will.</em></p>
<p>"Walter, are you able to find any method in this insanity?"</p>
<p>"Answer my question first, Adel."</p>
<p>"Ah, noble etiquette, right?" he leaned his back against the wall,
crossing his arms together. "Honor and glory should mean the same, but
they've both been mentioned. For me, honor's always been staying true to
one's convictions. We've all taken a vow to protect, which is why I was
dumbfounded when Cassius mentioned our heads."</p>
<p>"I've given it some thought as well, but it might have just been
phrasing. Instead of our heads, perhaps we just need proof?"</p>
<p>"Proof? What do you mean?"</p>
<p>Walter took his identification card out. "Right here. I was thinking
optimistically, that perhaps 'head' was just distasteful wording meant
to coerce us into unfathomable actions, perhaps he simply needs just
this. Remember the royal agents at Cathedral Hall? They searched for
identification, but the heads were discarded with the bodies." He then
dropped the identification of other warriors, showing how confident he
is with his hunch. "But that still doesn't align with honor, does
it?"</p>
<p>"It doesn't, but... you're starting to make some sense. Maybe
thinking optimistically is what he wants." Adel snickered, in a clearly
sarcastic way.</p>
<p>"Thinking optimistically is definitely a challenge created by the
trial. I even find myself demotivated when I try to think that way, as
it poses many risks. I believed this operation would just take a few
hours, but what if it goes on for multiple days? Random thoughts like
this, they create vulnerabilities, even if just for a moment."</p>
<p>"You're not gonna hide here the whole time, are you?"</p>
<p>"You won't either. I need you, Adel."</p>
<p>A look of confliction spread across his face. Adel was afraid of
death and failure. <em>I must... cure this ailment,</em> Walter
thought.</p>
<p>"Take a peek outside, Adel." Walter effortlessly carved the cave,
making an opening for them to see out. "Many of us have fallen, yet it
seems our numbers haven't gone down. The specters cannot imitate us to
perfection, and you can see this in the way they compose themselves. The
way they walk, their body language; it's not human enough. Can you see
it for yourself?"</p>
<p>"I can, but it's just not reliable enough."</p>
<p>"Can you confidently take twenty of their heads without slaying one
of our own?"</p>
<p>Adel's body tensed up a little, "I can't. I'm not cut out for this
kinda thing."</p>
<p>"Can you envision me taking forty for the both of us, then?"</p>
<p>"No way... there's only so much that one can do."</p>
<p>"Then I'll do it. For the time being, we'll think of other options.
But we have to pursue at least one of the available options."</p>
<p>Adel's body slowly descended until he was seated on the ground.
"You're sure? I feel like you can, but I just... can't imagine it."</p>
<p>"Allow me to show you." Walter removed his left shoulder plate,
casting his cloak aside. <em>Once he sees the crest of an Anima, he will
know.</em></p>
<p>"You..." Adel stood up.</p>
<p>"Hm?" <em>I haven't revealed the crest yet. What's with that reaction
and tone?</em></p>
<p>"Haha... I had a hunch after learning of your identity, how
intriguing!" Adel couldn't hold back his laughter, but he quickly
cleared his throat and fixed his posture, bowing his head. "I understand
now, Walter du Aesir. I will follow your orders."</p>
<p>"What is it? Why do you bow?"</p>
<p>"Are you gonna say there was even more for me to see? Your arm bears
the mark of the original Aesir bloodline. You're a bona fide descendent,
and..."</p>
<p><em>A sudden and long pause. I wasn't aware that being a descendent
was that big of a deal... and a descendent of whom? I wasn't sure there
was a direct bloodline. Is such an occurrence more special than being an
Anima?</em></p>
<p>"Walter, you're a descendent of Cain, aren't you?"</p>
<p>A sudden jolt ran through his entire body, as Walter took a step
forward. "Descendent... of Cain?"</p>
<p><em>A descendent of Cain? One of the four heroes? What leads him to
believe so? Why is this the first time I hear of this? Is it my physical
appearance? My abilities? The crest?</em></p>
<p>"What makes you say that, Adel?" Walter tried his hardest not to
impose a threatening aura.</p>
<p>"Were you going to show a crest of the Anima?" Adel followed up, as
if to read Walter's intentions.</p>
<p><em>Is it implied? Being a descendent of Cain, does this imply being
an Anima? What does he know?</em></p>
<p>"Adel, you too have the crest of the Aesir, I can see it. It's no
different than mine."</p>
<p>"Don't you also bear the crest of the Vanir?"</p>
<p>Walter nodded. Tension continued to build up from within him, but he
showed no sign of it.</p>
<p>Adel looked him in the eye. "It's not possible for an Aesir to bear
the crest of the Vanir. The two are strictly separate, the only
exception being direct descendents of the original."</p>
<p>As if to sense Walter's unease, Adel realized the dangers of
unloading too much information all at once. "I'm sure talk of this isn't
common among the royals, but it's known at the lower end of the
hierarchy. Us disposable folk pass these kinds of things down, the stuff
you'd hear at a feast." Adel concluded casually.</p>
<p><em>Can I trust his words? Similar to 'The Man at Peak's End', it's
more likely that his words are unpolished. Education is severely
filtered, but this might be a baseless rumor. I'll listen for now, just
so I can be aware of the possibilities.</em></p>
<p>"How can I trust your word?" Walter's tone was scrutinizing, but
hesitant.</p>
<p>"As an Anima, you possess exceptional perception. Look me in the
eyes, Walter. I'm not lying, am I?" Adel spread his arms out, as if to
put his everything on the line.</p>
<p><em>No signs of lying. His body language is sincere, and it lacks
method. He's not afraid nor elated, no sign of exploitation. He's not
calm, either. Compassionate? Pity for me? It was a mistake to ask, it's
not his word that I am concerned about; the information itself might be
faulty, and he wouldn't even know it.</em></p>
<p>The atmosphere of the room lost its tension, as if a burning flame
had been put out. A portion of the ground began to rise by Walter, as he
sat on the makeshift chair he created, signaling Adel to continue.</p>
<p>"Let me fill you in on some history. The Vanir are of the House of
Tilith, but the founder herself wasn't named Tilith Vanir. Her mother,
Lyra, continued to use the family name of Astid Baine. Tilith was no
different. Azura was a beautiful but weak nation, for a majority of the
warriors followed Cain to the new kingdom. Tilith worried for the
future, and she wanted our nation to pose a mighty legion to protect it.
This is why she founded the House of Tilith, focusing on preservation
instead of the House of Lyra's prosperity." Adel recalled softly.</p>
<p><em>The House of Lyra and the House of Tilith. A compromise to rule
the nation between the tenets of opulence and conservation. What he has
said so far matches what I was taught.</em></p>
<p>"Tilith went behind her mother's back, afraid that Azura would not be
able to defend itself in times of crisis. She ended up having an affair
with one of Cain's sons, a political affair that would be seen as a
breach of one of the seven codes, the Code of Fleur, should it have gone
public... is what Cain thought when he found out. But he wished to
protect his son and the daughter of his dearest friend. His son was
removed from his family and given a new one: Vanir. Cain also wished to
aid Tilith, and the lineage of the Aesir began as a result. While the
Aesir are not a direct bloodline, you should understand that there was
always an origin. And you, Walter, are a descendent of the first
Aesir... Cain."</p>
<p>"The first? I was told the origin was lost..."</p>
<p>"It's just speculation, but this is what I know. The Aesir lineage
are warriors trained for the purpose of protecting Azura. Cain had his
children join the ranks of the Azura military, and he relinquished his
position to another once he passed. The current ruler of Scyte is in no
way related to Cain, which is why that bandit-ridden area doesn't match
the description of its founder. True descendents of Cain will have both
the crest of Vanir and Aesir, that's why I was able to tell. The hero,
Cain, has to be the first Aesir, and your ancestor."</p>
<p>Walter seemed to have absorbed all of the information, as he began
considering the possibilities. "General Cassius... do you know if he is
one of these descendents?"</p>
<p>"You don't know?" Adel seemed let down. "I don't, either. I was
hoping you might be able to enlighten me, and tell me he was actually
your father. This kind of topic is usually kept private, you know. I'm
lucky enough that you don't know about it, otherwise I'd likely be
silenced..." Adel slowly looked in Walter's direction, with a slowly
growing look of terror in his eyes as if fear had planted itself deep in
him.</p>
<p><em>Not good, I lost control of my composure. I can't lose his trust
now, I need to learn more.</em> "Worry not. I have no authority to do
such a thing. As of now, you and I are equals." He re-equipped his
shoulder plate and glanced outside. Smoke filled the sky, it was a scene
straight out of a war. "I don't know who my father is. I was just
considering the possibility I may be related to him."</p>
<p>"You're pretty wise for your age." He reached for his pocket, but
suddenly jolted up as if to remember something. "Walter, my colleagues
are still out there. We split up during the grace period, but I think we
should regroup. Gathering numbers is best, wouldn't you agree?"</p>
<p><em>He has a point, but this also lets me observe how he is when he
reunites with others. I'll have to see if he relays anything to them,
anything regarding what I just learned about. I might also be able to
speak to them individually about it. This kind of thing requires time
and effort to process, and I have neither to spare at the
moment.</em></p>
<p>"I'll raise my left hand against adversaries. My right for allies.
Use this to guide your blade." Walter noted calmly.</p>
<p>"Understood."</p>
<p>"Describe them to me as we advance." Walter created an opening in the
cave, and they headed out. Within moments, the quality of the air
worsened severely as the smoke enveloped the skies above.</p>
<p>"Walter, is this poison? Are you alright?"</p>
<p>"Use your cloth. It's diluted, it shouldn't be lethal."</p>
<p>"I'm well versed in poisons, you don't have to worry about me too
much."</p>
<p>"Maintain your breathing. The poison and smoke have mixed together,
poison won't be as effective if you breathe into your cloth."</p>
<p>Adel's eyes closed and his eyebrows slanted. <em>Uhh... was he even
listening? I should catch up, Walter is rather fast.</em></p>
<p>"Let's move around the gorge, Walter. We should avoid the south
river, we don't want a confrontation with Babel."</p>
<p>"We might have to encounter him later. If it's inevitable, just stick
close with me. How many are we looking for?"</p>
<p>"Three. Two are around my height, one with red hair and the other
with brown. Another is taller, he wears a helmet with a horn, it should
be distinguishable."</p>
<p>"And the other two, anything distinguishable?"</p>
<p>Adel scratched his chin, as if he never stopped to consider what
makes them stand out. "The red head's got a curved sword, and he holds
it like a dagger. The other has a blue scarf. They all have the same
plated armor as me."</p>
<p>"Hold." Walter raised his left hand.</p>
<p>Adel leaned in to whisper, "What's ahead? And how can you tell?"</p>
<p>"They noticed us too soon. We're stealthily pacing, and the air is
dense. Follow my lead."</p>
<p>"They?" Adel threw in one more word before assuming a natural
position behind Walter. Two people in black cloaks came into view before
them. They extended their arms and began to speak.</p>
<p>"You two, what are your names?" <em>They sound normal. How can Walter
tell they're specters?</em></p>
<p>"I'm Owen. The one behind me is Gran."</p>
<p>The cloaked man on the left lowered his hood. He didn't match the
description, but spoke up. "I'm Luka, and this is Sebas. He doesn't
speak much. Where are you headed?"</p>
<p>"We're off to fight Cedar." <em>Cedar? Did he make that up on the
spot? What is Walter thinking?</em></p>
<p>"Do you mind if we join? I believe it would be best to fight in
groups." Luka extended his arm out.</p>
<p>Walter looked at the arm. <em>As I thought, the specters don't have
the same information as us. They don't know who exactly we are fighting.
This is... the best option.</em></p>
<p>"It's not so good to fight in groups actually." He looked earnestly
at Luka and Sebas before continuing. "Most of us are hiding in the
forest right now, where the air is much better. I think it's best to
head there."</p>
<p>Adel looked at Walter. <em>Are you serious? That kind of redirection
is so obvious, there's no way that---</em></p>
<p>"I understand. Thank you for your advice, we'll be on our way now,
Owen."</p>
<p>"Take care." Luka and Sebas began walking past them, but Walter spoke
up to them once more. "One other thing, there's a lake nearby. I
recommend exploring it, there's supposedly a powerful weapon in the
water. You might find it useful."</p>
<p>They parted ways. Walter continued onward, and Adel kept up.</p>
<p>"You're pretty fast, Adel."</p>
<p>"What was that performance just now? Was it fine that I stayed
silent?"</p>
<p>"Your body language was fine. The specters are still gathering
information, they're likely only fighting against Aesir who decided it
was best to kill one another."</p>
<p>"Your observations are beyond my comprehension."</p>
<p>"The river is ahead. Can you make eye contact with Babel?"</p>
<p>"Me? Why?"</p>
<p>He was silent as he continued. There was no doubt that Adel would
listen.</p>
<p>"Babel, where... ah! There he is" Adel looked at the man who was
currently fighting others. Even so, their eyes met shortly after. "He
saw me, Walter."</p>
<p>"Good, thank you. That's what I needed." <em>If Babel is aware of
Adel, that means he isn't a specter. It's best to check this possibility
out.</em> "Shall we continue north?"</p>
<p>"They are most likely here."</p>
<p>Walter scanned the area and began sprinting. Adel did his best to
follow. Two individuals, one tall with a helmet and the other with the
same armor, were in the distance. Adel was about to wave, but then
waited for Walter's signal; he didn't want to influence the two in any
way, so that Walter could properly assess them.</p>
<p>"They match the description." He raised his right arm, to which Adel
initiated his wave. They were reunited.</p>
<p>"Ga-"</p>
<p>"Not out loud." Walter didn't yell, but his voice was enough to stop
Adel from speaking.</p>
<p>"The both of you, do you know who this is?"</p>
<p>"Ewan..." The taller man spoke out, holding his hand towards Walter
for a handshake. "Thank you for protecting him." <em>A handshake
gesture? Did the two specters from before run into these two and learn
that?</em></p>
<p>Adel walked up to the taller man, who took his helmet off. "Garris,
where is Mace?"</p>
<p>Garrison paused for a moment. "He went to challenge Cassius..."</p>
<p>Adel backed up, nearly losing balance. "No... are you serious?"</p>
<p>The other man pulled a tattered scarf out before speaking. "Don't
worry, Adel... Mace will make it out. He's worthy, Cassius wouldn't kill
him."</p>
<p>Adel glanced at Walter, who was letting him catch up with his
companions.</p>
<p><em>It's not good if one of us is mentally burdened by another. Even
moreso if that other person isn't even here. I must do something about
it.</em> "Have faith, Adel." Those words gave him hope, coming from
Walter.</p>
<p>A shock suddenly decorated Adel's face, as if he remembered something
grand. "Oh, right! You two, this is Walter du Aesir. You won't believe
this, but he's... he's a true descendent!"</p>
<p>They both widened their eyes as Walter made his crests visible. He
seemed to be more convinced about the tale before, but he wanted more
details.</p>
<p>"I'll make a temporary shelter. Follow me."</p>
<hr />
<p>"Not only a true descendent, but he even has powers of earth like the
legendary Cain?!" said Garrison, who was sitting by the wall of the
makeshift cave.</p>
<p>"It's nothing special." Walter says, as everyone blankly stares at
him. Unlike the last shelter with Adel, Walter has created furniture
within the space. Six chairs and a table, an entirely separate room with
beds; even the dirt is softened to act as a pillow, as if anybody would
want to dirty their face. Adel couldn't help but smile after seeing
Walter's content showing-off face. <em>Wipe that smug off your face
Walter, you want to say that after making such a detailed hideout with
ease?</em></p>
<p>The scarfed man spoke up first to break the silence. "Right... oh, I
never introduced myself! I am Felix, and this is Garrison. The three of
us are all stationed at the same village, Mira."</p>
<p>"It's a pleasure to meet you so soon. I am Walter du Aesir, and I
am... not stationed?"</p>
<p>"You don't know? You seem pretty young, actually. What are you doing
here?" Felix expressed his interest, but Walter didn't want to waste any
time with small talk.</p>
<p>"I was called here, the same as you. I'd like to ask more
abo<em>---"</em></p>
<p>The ground shook. Walter did his best to maintain the structure of
the closed area, but the shaking was intense. He quickly opened up a
small hole to see what happened outside. The smoke became thicker, and
the specters began to run amok. Their distorted appearances slowly
changed from soldiers to their original forms. <em>Chastes... he's
trying to flee from the river? Babel and Theros are on the move, what's
going on?</em></p>
<p>The ground violently. Walter did his best to maintain the structure
of the closed area. He quickly opened up a small hole to see what
happened outside. The smoke became thicker, and specters began running
amok. Their once human appearances began to disfigure, unable to
coordinate properly with the sudden change of atmosphere. <em>Or
perhaps... is something external causing this? And Chastes, is he trying
to flee from the river? Theros is on the move, did Babel flee? Seeing
the water slowly rise from the gorge and spread out, it's
unnerving...</em></p>
<p>"Walter, what is it?"</p>
<p>"Adel, stay here. All of you stay put. The captains are on the move,
it seems like circumstances have changed."</p>
<p>Just then, the same thundering roar of Lord Michael filled the air.
"Halt your activities and fortify your defenses."</p>
<p>"Walter, don't go! That includes you. Lord Michael can handle this,
and Lord Cassius is here as well!"</p>
<p><em>Adel speaks the truth, I cannot imagine anybody that those two
cannot defeat. But there are other issues; there are nobles present,
this isn't a mere outburst. A targeted siege? At Queen Alice, or even
Hyland? I need to... no, I'm just making excuses. I want to go out
there.</em></p>
<p>"Adel, keep your comrades safe." His tone of voice was monotone, he
was entirely fixated on leaving. Nobody could stop him, as he created an
opening and closed it behind him.</p>
<p>A brief silence.</p>
<p>"It's rather dark here, don't you think, Adel?" spoke Garrison.</p>
<p>"Hold on." Adel struck his match on the ground, lighting a fire for a
small amount of light. On the floor were extra matches, and there was
now a circle that seemed to be made for creating a fire. He threw the
matches in and then dropped his own, lighting a fire.</p>
<p>"He's a considerate man, isn't he?" Felix took a seat by the fire,
noticing there were also rations of food. There was even a small opening
by the corner, which was likely an emergency escape. "So that's what a
true descendent is like. My faith in this country has been
restored."</p>
<p>"Adel?" Garrison stood up.</p>
<p>Adel held the cloth that belonged to Walter in his hand. It was well
made, but he could tell from the stitchings by the corners. <em>My
daughter used to make cloths for me, so I can tell. You don't know your
parents, you have a tone that feels so independent... and this cloth,
you made it yourself.</em> "Garrison, Felix. I'm gonna step out for just
a little while, I'll head back if anything happens. I'm too curious to
stay put."</p>
<hr />
<p>Distortions, a phenomenon pertaining to spectral entities. Common at
areas with leylines, distortions are the byproduct of psyche leakages
from leylines. There were several occurring all at once, an odd
occurrence.</p>
<p>"You, Walter du Aesir!" A voice yelled from behind him, he turned
back.</p>
<p>"Lord Babel?"</p>
<p>"Cut the honorifics, we're short on time. Find as many as you can,
help them evacuate."</p>
<p>"What's the situation?"</p>
<p>"The leyline by the plains, it's been destroyed completely. Emperor
class specters are spewing out."</p>
<p><em>The north? Master Darus is there... no, I should follow
orders.</em></p>
<p>Babel was nearly out of sight. Walter kept balancing between two
decisions: assist in battle, or help the many. <em>Honor and
glory...</em> he continued to think. <em>Is there a chance this is part
of the trial? Then, what I should do is help. I'll make temporary
shelters for everybody.</em></p>
<p>Before he could even think, the air around him began to thicken in a
mystifying fog. Psyche energy was leaking around him, as the distortion
began to fully envelop the surroundings. Beasts of cavalry and brigade
class began to take form from the fog, swarming Walter who began to
unsheathe his sword. The moment it left the scabbard, he parried a
strike from two beasts while keeping the rest in his vision. With
precise footwork, Walter turned to strike the specter on the left with
the handle of his blade. Pressing downward, he lifted himself to kick
the one next to him and boosted himself up to the larger specters. His
blade was aimed right for its head, before it suddenly changed its
appearance. <em>This one... Warlord class.</em></p>
<p>For perhaps a fraction of a second, the intelligent specter likely
prepared to strike back after fooling the Aesir. Upon gazing above,
however, the once weak blade seemed to tower over it with the presence
of a mountain. Though it remained the same in appearance, each fraction
of a second made it clear that the sword had changed. As it collided
first with its face, in the next instant it had already connected with
the ground, pulverizing anything in its path. As if to make up for the
delay, the rest of the body was immediately blasted away in the face of
such immense pressure, dust clouding any onlooker from viewing the
scene. As the air cleared up, nothing remained but a wide crater and a
sword now embedded onto the ground, waiting to be retrieved.</p>
<p><em>The placement of that distortion felt too targeted, I was at the
center of it. Somebody is behind this...</em></p>
<p><em>"Walter, do not reveal your abilities to anybody." Master spoke
these words to me, but I should at least be able to use that much. Even
if it's just a fraction, would I still be at a risk if nobody is
around?</em></p>
<p><em>...has it always felt this satisfying to use my
abilities?</em></p>
<p>Walter du Aesir, Unique Arts Technique: Coagulate. With his
heightened affinity for Earth, Walter is not only able to change not
only the material but the quality of the material. The secret to an
impactful strike with a thin weapon: massively increasing the density of
the blade at the right time of a swing.</p>
<p><em>I never had the chance to strike like this before, but physics
prefers heavier objects to stay on the ground. As I thought, crashing
downwards with the edge perpendicular to the ground makes for a stronger
impact.</em></p>
<p>"Hey, you!" A figure in the distance was catching up. "Where are you
headed?"</p>
<p>"...Babel?"</p>
<p>"Reporting in, Walter. What's our situation?"</p>
<p><em>That's right... outside of trial circumstances, I have more
authority than the brigade captains due to my status as Lord Charles'
underling. Then, earlier...</em></p>
<p>"Did you speak to me earlier?"</p>
<p>"No... I was fending off Chastes with Theros. We parted ways, he's
off to reconvene with Kevin. What happened?"</p>
<p>"This is... very grave. We mustn't waste time, come with me to the
plains!"</p>
<p>They both began sprinting quickly. <em>The specters that attacked me
just now, as well as the ones before, they assumed their original forms
or ambiguous forms. They could not imitate anymore, so what about the
Babel I saw...no, I interacted with earlier? And he knew my name, so
they can't be affiliated with the specters. I gave a false identity.
This is coordinated.</em></p>
<p>"Walter, is Darus in trouble?"</p>
<p>"Is there anyone else up north? There was an imitation of you that
told me to protect or evacuate the others, they likely wanted me to give
their positions away."</p>
<p>"Was it that similar?"</p>
<p>"Even down to their aura, it was no different from you." Walter
peeked at Cathedral Hall, but he couldn't sense Cassius. "Where is Lord
Cassius?"</p>
<p>"He's protecting the royals. Lord Michael has gone to the scene of
the destruction... it should be around where Darus is?"</p>
<p>"We have no time to waste. It's just up ahead."</p>
<p>Walter suddenly paused. He analyzed his surroundings before turning
around completely. Babel continued forward, knowing that if his sudden
halt had anything to do with him he would have signaled it.</p>
<p>"Adel, why are you here?"</p>
<p>"Don't worry, they're still in the shelter. It's closed too, I spent
a good amount of time fortifying it. Let me help, please."</p>
<p>"I don't have time to deny you, keep up with me." He dashed forward.
Surprisingly, Adel was pacing well behind him as they approached the
plains. A massive wall of mist stretching as high as the clouds. Several
emperor class beasts were shaping in the air and rising from the ground.
Babel had already begun exterminating them, but just up ahead was the
true struggle: the destruction of the leyline vein had spawned a miasma,
a powerful type of specter that is formless besides its unique trace,
which is mist in this case. It covered almost the entire plains, and
within it was likely Darus.</p>
<p>"Babel, I'm going in!" Walter called out as he passed him.</p>
<p>"Stay cautious, the both of you!"</p>
<p><em>The mist is getting thicker... I can feel my sense of space
warping.</em></p>
<p>On the other side of the miasma was a hellish scene. Lord Michael was
doing battle with two masked individuals, and Darus was taking on what
seems to be a judgement class specter.</p>
<p><em>Lord Michael is moving around in the air at such absurd speeds,
and the two he is fighting are keeping pace. I must assist
Darus.</em></p>
<p>"Adel, don't get killed."</p>
<p>"I'll stand my ground. Let me witness this."</p>
<p>Walter lunged in, and Darus could sense his presence. The specter
took the form of a four-armed ogre, with a blade in each hand. Its face
was intimidating, and its horns could be used as weapons as well.
<em>This kind of enemy shouldn't be that difficult... but Darus isn't
using his abilities. This must be a move of intelligence for whoever is
behind this, I should be wary as well.</em></p>
<p>"It's good to see you, Walter." He could see it in his eyes, Walter
already understood why he must not use his powers here. War is about
knowing the intention of the enemy.</p>
<p>"Our arm count should be fair now."</p>
<p>"Cracking jokes at a time like this? Hah, you never change!"</p>
<p>The two entered a stance specific for dual battle, one that they have
practiced together many times before. Walter had his back to Darus,
their blades aligning. With the first step, Walter dashes to the side as
Darus heads straight on.</p>
<p><em>That beast is just going to use its other arms for Walter, right?
What an interesting young man...</em></p>
<p>As the specter lashed its blade at Walter, not a single drop of blood
hit the floor. Walter used his blade to withstand the first strike, then
grabbed the opposite end of the ogre's blade with his hand. In a swift
motion, Walter pulled down on his sword and up with his knee against the
adversary's blade. With his sheer strength alone, he shattered the
sword. Another blade was coming, but Walter parried it by the lower half
of his sword. The ogre's blade nearly grazed Walter's face, but he
grabbed onto the blade and fought back against the force. The moment the
ogre's pressure weakened, Walter gripped the sword's edge and boosted
himself up until he stood on the blade like a platform.</p>
<p>With grace, Walter leapt high into the air. <em>Now, it's all you,
Darus. Its attention is on me.</em></p>
<p>Darus, God General of Swords, Unique Arts Technique: Magma Blade.
Combining his affinity for fire and earth, Darus creates another sword
with the properties of a miniature volcano. Hot to the touch, with a
sharp molten core and an outer shell that is brittle but rough. In one
slash, the blade shattered and doused the specter with lava. It began to
shriek and strike Darus, who then parried the other swords with his
own.</p>
<p>"Walter!"</p>
<p>Shortly after the shout, a sharp blade quickly fell down right
through the head of the specter. A loud thud followed by the monsters'
blades hitting the ground, before it began to vanish. Walter fell
shortly after to pick his sword up, which was now lodged into the
ground. <em>Perpendicular for force, and parallel for power.</em></p>
<p>"Master Darus, the emperor class specters aren't present. All that's
left are the two that Lord Michael is fighting."</p>
<p>"Don't worry, leave it to him. Our goal now is to de-escalate and end
this bout. You did good, Walter, I'm proud of you."</p>
<p>"No, I... used some of my power at the end. I could tell that I
wasn't supposed to."</p>
<p>"Don't worry about it, the enemy couldn't flee because it's dead. You
could see its core hit the ground."</p>
<p>Adel walked over to the two who were having a brief celebration.
"That was amazing!"</p>
<p>Walter had a slight smirk of satisfaction, and Darus could tell.
<em>Looks like you've done some socializing, Walter. This was more than
Cassius could ask for.</em></p>
<hr />
<p>Shortly after Adel had left the hideout, Garrison and Felix were
afraid he may never return. Adel had always been the headstrong type
like Mace, but he had a softness in his heart. To alleviate their
worries, they headed to the other room to rest. Though they were both
unwilling to be vulnerable, a sudden wave of fatigue caught up with the
both of them.</p>
<p>Adel sat by the fire. "Garrison, Felix. Do you think Mace will come
back?"</p>
<p>No response. It appears they are sound asleep in the other room,
until some footsteps could be heard. "Have faith in him, Adel."</p>
<p>"Felix, you're up?"</p>
<p>"I'm still thinking about that descendent. He's an interesting
person." Felix stood by Adel and smiled. "Welcome back, Adel."</p>
<p>His face then moved over to the opening that he walked out of. It
was... very roughly patched. "Is that... supposed to be a door?"</p>
<p>"Oh, that? I wanted to get some fresh air for a bit, and I also
wanted to see what the surrounding was like. It wasn't that dangerous
out so I stayed a bit, but I realized how vulnerable I was and quickly
tried to re-fortify it."</p>
<p>"Haha, some things never change, eh?"</p>
<p>"On that note, I wanted to talk with Walter more. He's an Anima as
well, he's got the full package"</p>
<p>"Is that so? Maybe we can find him again after all this."</p>
<p>"I'd hope so."</p>
<p>"You really gave me a surprise, though. When I saw him next to you,
he had such a strong aura! I thought maybe you've been walking around
with one of the warlord-class."</p>
<p>Adel stood up and began approaching Felix.</p>
<p>"Adel?"</p>
<p>"Hey, Felix. You trust me, right?"</p>
<p>"Of course. I knew you would find us again, but you know how Mace
is... he's stubborn and wanted a quick way to win. Don't let that
demotivate you."</p>
<p>"That's good." A short but eerie pause. "Can you stand by the wall?
The one next to the exit, I'm trying to get a good measure down. Maybe
we'll need to escape, I'd like to soften a part of the wall."</p>
<p>"What about the area you fortified?"</p>
<p>"Ah... that? It's actually a lot stronger now, come on just do
it."</p>
<p>"Alright, alright! I know you're so meticulous about things like
this." Felix walked over and lined up against the wall. He began to
turn, until...</p>
<p>A long, crystal blade impaled him through the chest, going as far as
to strike through the wall as well.</p>
<p>"A...del?"</p>
<p>The figure that looked like Adel had its arms raised, with a blade
between each finger. The four blades crashed downward along with the
movement of his arms, slicing Felix into four pieces. The walls were
decorated red, and not a single sound could be made in time.</p>
<p>"A talkative bunch, simply not my type." It glanced over at the wall.
" There's another in the other room, right?"</p>
<p>It walked over, slowly revealing its true form. Standing over the
tall man lying down was a woman with a single seraphim wing, seemingly
stitched to her back. She had a frilly black dress and a white
under-piece, typical for nobles to wear. Instead of pupils, her eyes had
a sharp cross that stared coldly at the man before her. Barefoot, and
now holding a crystal sword in her hand, she blitzed it into Garrison's
neck.</p>
<p>And then his head.</p>
<p>And then his chest.</p>
<p>And then his stomach.</p>
<p>The stabs turned into slices, and the slices turned into
carvings.</p>
<p>Until there was nothing left of Garrison but a crimson mess.</p>
<p>"I don't need to preserve the useless ones, so making art like this
is perfectly reasonable!"</p>
<p>Two other voices began to echo.</p>
<p>"Innamorati, did you learn more?" A light, more feminine voice. The
sound of metal clashing made it clear she was still in battle.</p>
<p>She dropped her sword, as it shattered to pieces and faded away. "Our
target is Walter du Aesir. Is he there?"</p>
<p>"Sorry, love, but our hands are a bit busy!" A deeper voice, but more
energetic and rather sarcastic.</p>
<p>"I'll be there. The general won't leave the center, he's afraid of
attacks. I'll send Ashura their way to make sure of it." Innamorati
brought forth another blade, she was eager to get into the action.</p>
<p>The deep voice seemed to be indifferent to the fight. "Do what you
want, dear! Just don't break my toys! Oho!" It was very clear how
intense of a battle the two were in, yet their demeanor was scarily
composed.</p>
<p>Emerging from the cave, Innamorati scanned for her target while
disguised as Adel. She pursued north, until finally seeing him.</p>
<p>She chuckled to herself. "Luck is on my side today, huh?"</p></content>
        <category term='	chapter'/><link rel='alternate' href='https://enceris.github.io/p/1'/>
        <id>https://enceris.github.io/p/1</id>
        <published>1970-01-01T05:30:01+05:30</published>
        <updated>1970-01-01T05:30:01+05:30</updated>
        <summary>	THE REFORMER</summary>
        <a href='/p/1' class='bold'>	The Grand Gathering</a>
        <content type='html'><p>--&gt;</p>
<p><em>Clad with the blood of either friend or foe, the original shine
of the blade could barely be recognized. Gone are the days of prosperity
and kinship, for the era upon him was grim and full of carnage and evil.
The man once sought truth followed the trail of deceit, and he now finds
himself at a loss of who to call his ally. There was no land that held
its rightful ruler, yet all of mankind seemed to agree to a mutual
bloodshed and malice. Wrath was the only common denominator on this
continent, yet he spoke boldly to catch the attention of the beast
before him. "The lands, they must be cleansed. These people, they must
be saved." Such drivel should be ignored by the strong, for the words of
the weak were meant to be trampled. Yet the man challenged the Heralds
of Death with his words alone: "The strong does not yet exist as it once
had. Order will find itself as the mighty returns." These Heralds, who
have abused kinship to conjure fear, found trepidation in the man that
spoke these words. They exhausted all of their forces to claim his head
but to no avail. "Thy speak of the strong not existing, the strong be
returning, you dare not refer to thyself?" spoke the head of Regulus, to
which the man replied, "To compare the strong to the likes of you and I,
we are helpless at its mercy. The worth of your head, and the worth of
mine, we are but dust in his eyes. Your provocations would not even
appear in the cognizance of the strong." Despite his admonishments, the
man was hunted to the point of self-exile, for there was no land that
did not desire his blood splattered across the floors. This man yearned
not for the strong, yet could not help but express his bitterness, for
the weak have gathered together to expedite another's decay. Yet in his
eyes, he too was of the weak, and it was his duty to see to it that the
strong would one day return. "Demiurgos meets Invictus, Life meets
Death," thus spoke the man.</em></p>
<p>Sitting in his lonesome, he recalled his favorite excerpt from an old
tale, <em>The Man at Peak's End.</em> At both an unknown time and
setting, this tale depicts a prodigy that was denounced by his country
and his people for his bold prophecies. To prevent his loved ones from
being slain, the man fled and vanished into obscurity; what remains now
is a mysterious story with no definitive end. Although this tale is
greatly shadowed by the likes of <em>The Four Heroes</em> and <em>The
Peerless Warlord</em>, he found this specific tale much more intriguing
and charming. <em>Perhaps it was the lack of details and
popularity,</em> he thought to himself, <em>that the work had a sense of
credibility that would have been left untouched since its writing. No
exaggeration, and nothing inserted for the purpose of entertainment; a
raw piece of history depicting a time in which this flourishing world
housed the most incredulous of prosecutors. The less infamy a work has,
the more merit it boasts</em>, he concludes. After all, the work has no
other versions, meaning its words have never been tampered from its
original creation. While it remains a mystery with many questions left
unanswered, he felt a connection with this story. It shined a bright
light on many importances of his life.</p>
<p>"Ah, that's right," he spoke out, before looking around the training
room in search of people. He sensed a presence entering, but it wasn't
one to be wary of. A memory resurfaced in his mind, and he dropped the
eighty kilogram weight that he was lifting with his left arm. Standing
up, he reached into his pocket to pull out a small notebook as he walked
over to one of the training dummies. Then, he proceeded to open the
notebook and begin writing as he spoke out:</p>
<p>"This world follows seven core principles, and you will learn more
about them and their origins when you grow older. They are named after
the individuals who were the subject of worship. These are very
important to understand, so listen to me carefully as I tell you these
codes.</p>
<p>The Code of Avita: One in power cannot be forcefully dethroned, it is
the decision for the masses to decide who to follow.</p>
<p>The Code of Yggdrasil: One is not allowed to deprive another of their
merriment.</p>
<p>The Code of Krotek: One may be enslaved only without
mistreatment.</p>
<p>The Code of Imperion: One can prevent a war or stop it, for war does
not have to see its end.</p>
<p>The Code of Fleur: One's chastity, marriage, and love is destined by
oneself. False love, arranged marriages, and the deprivation of one's
virginity is taboo.</p>
<p>The Code of Sohee: One can be indicted, but cannot be punished
without integrity.</p>
<p>The Code of Ignis: One will not find salvation in taking one's own
life.</p>
<p>If these kinds of things interest you, I can provide you with <em>The
Seven Vows,</em> which contains everything there is about these codes
and the individuals. There's also history, but... before learning about
history, it's important to know about the now. This is the Luminous
continent, home to the Three Kingdoms: Ingram, the nation of scholars
and wisdom. Located further north at the east coast of the continent,
the ruler of the nation is also the headmaster of their famous academy.
Many important discoveries have been made there, and I have nothing but
respect for them. At the center of the nation is the Armament, one of
the most secure research facilities. Bordering Ingram to the south west
is Scyte, a nation of battle known as the 'land of the mercenaries.'
Ruled by one man and his generals, Scyte is mostly known for its
military might and their fearsome God Generals. These individuals have
the potential to be the strongest in the land. Lastly, bordering Scyte
as well as the east coast of this continent is Azura, the nation of
prosperity and honor. This is where we are, a beautiful empire ruled
over by two noble houses. Everybody in our nation is at peace, and we
have not seen conflict in centuries. Within the continent, as well as
other continents, is a hub for the Imperial Order; you may come to know
this faction as simply the 'Guild.' Here, in Azura, is where this
embassy resides.</p>
<p>About the Imperial continent, it is one of the most historic and rich
continents. This continent houses the Regal Kingdoms, which controls the
Guild and was once ruled by one of the Seven: Imperion. The continent is
also where Allanon, the great Elven woods, reside. Just east of it is
Adneil, the imperial Elven nation. Another one of the Seven, Fleur, was
a revered figure in this country."</p>
<p>"Walter, are you speaking to yourself?" Before he could continue,
Walter was interrupted by a man who had been at the entrance for some
time. "Am I interrupting?"</p>
<p>"As always, you have no presence. I could only sense your entering,
but afterwards it was nearly impossible to follow, Master Darus."</p>
<p>"That was an awfully long speech, I'd love to ask its purpose but I'm
afraid I don't have the leisure to do so."</p>
<p>"Oh?"</p>
<p>"Cassius has ordered me to inform you, all of the Aesir from across
the continent have been called to gather at the Cathedral Hall. Although
you are still young and in training, he specified that you must attend
as well."</p>
<p>He walked away from the dummy and reached over to a table, placing
his notebook down. "This sounds rather important. Are there any other
details?"</p>
<p>Darus shook his head, looking downwards. Walter always picks up on
small gestures such as these.</p>
<p>"I can only inform you of the orders. However, I can inform you on
what to expect. After all, the Aesir that will be there are not all from
Azura..."</p>
<p>Darus continued to debrief, but unbeknownst to him he had begun
explaining to a sturdy wall. Although Walter had utmost respect for him,
hearing his voice reminds him of the authorities in the continent. Born
to nobility, yet never participating in it, Walter was born to be a
warrior and has been separated from the families at a young age,
training in solemn alone-ness.</p>
<p><em>I was taken in by Lord Luminous, who gave me 'The Man at Peaks
End.' I recall the words as clear as ever from the tale... 'You four,
you shall carry my burden; no, my hopeless dreams. You endure hardship,
pain, struggle and suffering not because you are weak. No, this
experience accumulates because it is destined for the strong to never
yield to such barbarism. Let it stack over and over, for I truly believe
such mundane tasks do not even render in your eyes. You four, your
greatness and strength is guaranteed. I shall see to it, even when my
bearings have transcended this world, that you will become that which
I... which they have... no, that which YOU have envisioned yourself. The
weak must not decide for the strong, and the strong must find a role to
assume to present to the weak. These ramblings of mine, I pray you four
shall cherish it dearly for eons to come; for when the strong remember
me so, I shall be the reminder to them of you who serve as the
origin.'</em></p>
<p>"Walter..."</p>
<p>A young man, standing tall with his hands over an open notebook. He
looked downwards in self-absorbed focus. <em>This was the sight of a man
deep in thinking and mourning</em>, Darus thought to himself.</p>
<p>"Very well then," Walter utters, closing the notebook as he
approaches Darus. "I will go."</p>
<p>"How long has it been since you last left this place?"</p>
<p>"Seven months, eight days, fifteen hours."</p>
<p><em>Precise, exact. This man was separated from his family at a young
age to cultivate what he is now, how monstrous.</em></p>
<p>As Walter walked past Darus, a sense of absolute conviction emitted
from the young boy. Darus was used to these kinds of auras, but seldom
did he feel it from somebody still in their youth. Walter had just
recently turned eighteen, but he already has the abilities of a
long-time warrior.</p>
<p>Closing the door, Walter pointed at the only decoration hung up. "Did
you notice? My sword's sheath is on the door that you walked through.
But the sword itself, I always leave it elsewhere."</p>
<p>"You've learned since that incident, I can see that."</p>
<p>Silence followed. He brought the sheathe down and equipped it to his
waist. "I won't be treated that way a second time." He then walked to
the training dummies, where he removed its head and lifted a stainless
broadsword from within the body.</p>
<p>"It still perplexes me, Walter," Darus took a seat by the dummy near
him. "This sword that I gave you, it was unbelievably light when I last
picked it up. Such a thin blade, it's terrifying how much impact you are
able to give it with each swing."</p>
<p>"You noticed this is the same blade?"</p>
<p>"Though it's untouched, I can see that you polish it with care. I can
always get you a new, higher quality one."</p>
<p>"There's no need for that."</p>
<p>"I don't mean to underestimate your abilities as an Anima, but having
a better weapon never hurts." <em>After all, the quality of the blade
hasn't decreased since I gave it to you. Has it gotten even better,
actually?</em></p>
<p>Walter sheathed his sword and tidied up his boots.</p>
<p>"At some point, you'll come to a revelation that not any sword can
work for you. Imperion himself had his own specific equipment, soon you
will be the same. It's a warrior's specialty."</p>
<p><em>Although his interpretation of warrior spirit and understanding
of warrior culture is completely accurate... I am sure he would find it
difficult to believe the properties of the sword,</em> Walter thought to
himself. In this world, there is a universal force that exists within
every being: Psyche. A person's psyche is determined at birth, and
psyche is measured in terms of affinity. Each race has different
affinities, but there are only four of them. For humans like Walter,
they wield the affinities of four elements: Fire, Water, Earth, or Wind.
The title of Anima is given to those that have the highest affinity for
their respective element, a traditional practice of the Luminous
continent. <em>I am the Anima of Earth, and my sword is... a completely
normal broadsword that can be purchased anywhere at any local smithery.
I know that much. The abilities that Anima are capable of, the ones that
I had spent so much time learning, makes us several magnitudes stronger
than the common folk. My ability to turn weak material into powerful
ones, that is what I specialize in. So... I am sorry, but I won't be in
need of a signature weapon. Not any time soon.</em></p>
<p>"Let's go, the carriage is waiting for us."</p>
<p>"Understood."</p>
<p>Walter's gaze was fixed, and his resolve was hardened. He suddenly
became more aware of the events that awaited him, as his eyes flared in
fervor.</p>
<p>"And before we get on, I'd like to remind you of something."</p>
<p>Darus paused for a brief moment, then continued walking forward. He
could sense the burning aura behind him, but that aura almost diminished
entirely after he halted.</p>
<p>Walter analyzed the man in front of him. <em>His back stiffened, and
his shoulders rose just slightly. His chest is out more, and his walking
became more rhythmic. He spoke these words with an ominously casual
tone. I had rationalized that there must be a reason for this. Perhaps
his own consciousness, or maybe he is being watched?</em></p>
<p>"Fear kills warriors that don't mend it to their will. Walter du
Aesir..."</p>
<p>Before Walter could return to his state of ardent preparation, Darus
exerted a dominating and suffocating aura. It was as if the man that was
just in front of him was now towering over him, and he was merely an
insect that his shadow mistook for the ground.</p>
<p>"You haven't felt that fear as much as you need to."</p>
<p>The aura dissipated, as they both carried on. <em>Perhaps, this will
prevent him from making mistakes due to his eagerness. I don't mean to
scare you more than life already has, my student. This is for your own
good.</em></p>
<hr />
<p>Cathedral Hall was a place in which only a single aspect of it
warranted an accurate name. Although there is a cathedral-like entrance
and a tower at the center, the area itself had no halls nor did it
resemble a cathedral. It was a wide circular building, encased within a
dome of protection. The area around this hall was known as "Babylon's
Hell," because it prevents normal people from being able to reach the
center due to its harsh conditions. The entire area itself serves as
both training grounds and a containment zone. A large leyline vein
passes through this area, and to the west of it is what's known as a
leyline deposit. Leyline veins are currents that run through this world
that carry energy, which can be converted into psyche. To prevent
leyline deposits from being too rich in psyche, the Vanir family makes
breaches into large leyline veins across the country. Specters, beings
created from the energy that passes, spawn from these veins. These
entities are harmful and considered monsters. They take a multitude of
forms and slay indiscriminately. As warriors of Azura, we must learn the
many different archetypes of specters as well as the range at which
their strength may vary. But of course, traversing Babylon's Hell and
reaching Cathedral Hall should not pose any life-threatening difficulty
to an Aesir.</p>
<p>The Aesir have absolute loyalty to the Vanir despite being a more
powerful family. The Aesir have much larger numbers, as well as the most
skilled fighters of the continent, while the Vanir represent one of the
two houses that rule Azura, the House of Tilith. The other house,
represented by Aidan Baine, is the House of Lyra. Walter, being
exceptionally loyal to the Vanir, cared very little for the House of
Lyra.</p>
<p>Darus leaned forward in the carriage to grab Walter's attention, who
was spacing out. "While we are here, do you mind if I ask what your talk
was about?"</p>
<p>"Are you referring to back at the training hall?"</p>
<p>"I am. It was a little unnerving to hear you speak in such a soft
tone. It felt unusual, but humorous at the same time."</p>
<p>"Lord Charles Vanir will be having a new child soon, and I have been
appointed to this child by Lord Luminous himself. I was practicing my
teaching methods."</p>
<p>"I see. When do you expect to have that talk with the child?"</p>
<p>With a stern face, he uttered, "After they are born."</p>
<p>Darus burst out in laughter, and even the carriage driver couldn't
help but chuckle. "You know, kid, you never fail to amuse me."</p>
<p>"I was serious, it would be best for them to learn this as soon as
possible."</p>
<p>"You're not much of a teacher, are you?"</p>
<p>"I'm merely imitating you."</p>
<p>"That's a different case, Walter. You were a genius, it was easy to
teach you everything at once. But not everyone's as gifted as you,
you'll have to wait and see what that child is capable of. I know I'm
not much of a teacher, but I know that much at least."</p>
<p>"Your teachings have influenced me greatly, mind you. I believe
you've done splendidly. In your honor, I will make sure the child grows
up well."</p>
<p>Darus scratched his head and looked beyond the horizon. "Not
listening to me, are you? You took away all the difficulty of teaching,
you should observe someone else. Pick up a pupil or two later on,
perhaps the struggle will shape you into a good instructor."</p>
<p>"A pupil... would that be appropriate for me?"</p>
<p>"Let go of the past, Walter. You're not some trainee anymore. I've
seen what you can do, you're already a full fledged warrior. But you're
still not ready, Walter du Aesir. You still need the experience."</p>
<p><em>Experience? This came about suddenly. Perhaps this event at
Cathedral Hall... this is an experience necessary for me. Lord Cassius
wants me there, but all of the Aesir have gathered. The meaning of
this...</em></p>
<p>"I know that very well. Thank you, Master Darus."</p>
<p>"That being said, don't overload the child with all that damn
information! Make it thorough, what's the kid gonna do after learning
such an important code from a single sentence, huh?!"</p>
<p>"That's... a very good point." He took his notebook out and began
writing. Once more, he was fully engrossed and had become that sturdy
wall. "How might I make this optimal for their survivability?" he
mumbled to himself.</p>
<p>Darus laughed again, "Survivability, eh? I guess you can't argue with
that!"</p>
<p>"Master?"</p>
<p>He brought his hand closer to Walter's head, then extended his index
finger. "Whatever's in here, it's enough to make a rough man like me
chuckle. That's how I'm sure you'll be a good mentor."</p>
<p><em>He continued onward, seeming content with my responses. I will
admit, after thinking about what I said I am rather embarrassed. It's
rather silly after considering that I am talking about a child... but he
doesn't seem to realize that this is the child of Lord Charles, the most
powerful man in Azura. There's no doubt their potential will supersede
us both.</em></p>
<hr />
<p>Arriving at Cathedral Hall was a surreal feeling to Walter. He had
never been around so many people before, let alone his own kindred. At
the center of the hall was Lord Cassius, the director of the Aesir
legion, and the general of the Azuran Imperial Guard. On his left stood
three individuals: Theros, the captain of the first imperial brigade;
Arthur, captain of the fourth; Lord Michael, the first God General of
Scyte. Michael's presence alone escalated the significance of today's
events. To the right of Cassius: Babel, captain of the second and Kevin,
captain of the third. Darus left Walter's side and walked up the steps,
positioning himself to the rightmost. <em>Lord Michael and Lord Cassius,
and all of the brigade captains. Master Darus, as well. Just what is in
store for us?</em></p>
<p>Just then, the murmur of the crowd was interrupted by Cassius. "Five
hundred and twelve heads on this continent claim the title of Aesir.
Only four hundred and eighty-three of you are present. At least eight of
you have died on the way here, and the rest could not make it. The
latter two groups, of course, are no longer Aesir."</p>
<p>Only a few voices continued in the crowd. A majority remained silent
and composed. Walter was perplexed that some could not make it to
Cathedral Hall, even more at the fact that some had died. A few chuckles
within the crowd struck a nerve within Walter, a taunt for the fallen.
<em>Not every Aesir is the same as I</em>, he thought to himself.
<em>Master Darus could not have been more accurate. The crowd is
confused, worried, eager, and speculatory. No such meeting has ever
taken place on a scale this grand, so why now?</em></p>
<p>"Silence!" Darus' voice roared out, as the captains began walking
down the steps. Darus followed shortly after, and the crowd made way for
them. One by one, they left the hall. Whether the silence was out of
fear or respect, it continued long after the captains were out of
sight.</p>
<p>"Those of you that know of what will transpire today, remain
standing. The rest of you, please be seated or kneel." It was as if
Cassius' voice casted a spell of obedience, as hundreds of Aesir were
brought to their knees. <em>Nearly everyone, including myself, kneeled
to the ground and looked up in scrutiny. There were about twelve or
fourteen people remaining standing. From their composure, I could see
the dread and fear that flooded their being. What exactly is going
on?</em></p>
<p>"Very well then." A soft whirring could be heard, but no one dared to
pinpoint its location. Then, in an instant---<em>BANG!</em> The men that
were standing fell to their ground, their headless bodies clashing with
those who kneeled. Those that remained did not dare leave their current
positions. <em>The heads of the deceased were all pierced with spears
connected to ropes, with a force great enough to completely remove it
from the body. Just what would happen had they have missed?</em> "Search
their bodies for identification. Find me their drill instructor. We
shall have them executed. Let this be an ultimatum to all of you, when
you have your own disciples and underlings: whatever occurs today,
should you ever become a superior... you will speak not of this."</p>
<p><em>Dead silence. Fear. The sound of death. The aura of control. All
of these are present around me right now. Royal agents rummaged through
the corpses, and as the agents left, Cassius ordered us all to stand.
Many trembled, very few maintained their composure. They were hesitant
to stand, but even more hesitant to disobey. I was the fourth person to
stand, even if the first bunch did in an instant.</em></p>
<p>"Each of you will return to Babylon's Hell. We have serrated the vein
that flows below us to its limit. You have a few tasks, but you need
only complete one: take the head of twenty specters; bring the heads of
at least ten of your own kind; defeat one of the captains in a fight
after finding them, they will not kill you but I doubt you would be able
to kill them if you tried. Lastly, if you wish, you may challenge me
right here. However, if I deem you unworthy, I will take your life."
Several robed individuals entered the hall, making their way to the
center.</p>
<p><em>In just a few moments, everything had changed. The minds of us,
the Aesir, could not comprehend what had just happened that quickly. I
could see people tremble, and a few try their best to remain composed.
Their bodies begin to precipitate, and it accumulates by their
fingertips and the edge of their head. Their gaze becomes fixated, but
occasionally relaxes. I wonder, just what kind of reaction would my body
be having from another perspective? Lord Cassius... I respect this man
greatly. Even as he prepares to send me to my possible death, I look up
to him in reverence. Am I smiling? I can feel the tension on my face,
but... I don't think my mind has caught up yet. This trial, can it be a
trial? A death sentence? A chance to reveal my capabilities, to show
everyone what I am capable of? Is this... really the right time to feel
such profuse thrill?</em></p>
<p>One of the figures removed their robe. It was Morgaine Ballard, a
noble of the Vanir family. "There will be a grace period of three hours.
All spectral beasts have been neutralized, but will be free to move once
this period ends. No killing or fighting shall take place in these three
hours. Use this time to your advantage, please remain here if you wish
to challenge Cassius." Her voice was cold and unforgiving.</p>
<p>A familiar figure made her way from behind Cassius. After removing
her hood, the crowd began to kneel.</p>
<p>"L-Lady Alice!"</p>
<p>"Her Majesty!"</p>
<p>She motioned her arm outward, urging the warriors to lift their
heads. "I am sure my presence here is a surprise for you. But this isn't
a matter that concerns only the people of Azura. This is why Lord
Michael is here as well."</p>
<p>The man himself stepped forward. A few of the warriors fell back from
their kneeling. Just one footstep, a shockwave of his power was enough
to frighten beasts.</p>
<p>"Queen Alice li Vanir will make the closing remarks," another hood
went down, it was Hyland Baine, a high ranking member of the House of
Lyra.</p>
<p>The queen stepped forward, looking from the left to the right. "I
have high hopes for all of you. Although normally the head of that many
specters is enough, I believe that the head of an Aesir alone would be
worth a hundred specters... you get me? This trial is not only a
measurement of passage, but keep in mind the importance of glory and
honor."</p>
<p><em>So this is a trial to their eyes. Her tone, it's oddly casual. Is
she unaware of what had just happened to a few of us? No, that can't be.
Glory and honor... It's as if she spoke to fan the flames of treachery
as well. High hopes for all of us, but it seems the easiest route would
be to turn on one another, especially after valuing each of us at that
level of praise. This... reminds me of 'The Man at Peak's End', this
sense of ambiguity that I feel. The possibility of not being able to
determine who is an ally, only being able to confirm foes through
battle. This thrill... it's as if these circumstances were ordained by
fate.</em></p>
<p><em>TIME TO BATTLE: 2:57:04</em></p>
<p><em>People left in groups, or on their own. It seemed that nobody
wanted to stay to challenge Cassius... I definitely didn't, either.
Cassius is renowned for his terrifying abilities. Lord Cassius went
toe-to-toe with Lord Michael of Scyte before, a man strong enough to
cleave mountains. I'd imagine he would cut everyone down in one hit,
claiming that those unable to survive one attack aren't worthy to live.
Luckily for us, Babylon's Hell was a large forested area, with different
unique zones. The forest becomes notably denser further west, and there
is a large lake south east. Up in the north is a plains area with a lot
less trees. Directly east has a gorge that separates this area and the
border of Lyra, one of the graceful cities of Azura. The river coming
from the lake pours out as a waterfall into this gorge. From the looks
of it, many sought out others to form teams, while others began laying
traps---Alice's words have pushed many of us to think of murder, it
seems.</em></p>
<p><em>For an Aesir, we don standard gear for soldiers. The difference
between us and a regular soldier is our tacit uniqueness in battle; we
all have our own different methods of fighting. A few of us are armed
with various secondary weapons, some of us carry shields, some prefer
cloaks over gear. With my abilities, taking ten heads would be more than
easy for me... but something about Alice's words irks me. Perhaps it's
an option, but not the right one. I'm sure many of us believe this is
the easiest route, but seeing as Cassius did not give much care to any
individual's life... it's just another test?</em></p>
<p><em>TIME TO BATTLE: 2:18:22</em></p>
<p><em>I have situated myself atop one of the trees. This location
grants me a good view of the plains and the lake, as well as enough
security to be safe from a ranged attack. I have been pondering whether
or not I should spill the blood of my brethren. Glory and honor, they
have been stated but not defined... what would they mean in the eyes of
the common man? We are warriors, and we think different from those we
protect. Is it really honorable to take from others, to steal an
opportunity, a life? This trial seems too straightforward. The risk of
challenging what seems to be the clear answer is high as well. I need to
clearly assess what I know. After scouting about, it seems that the
specters are much more dangerous than made out to be. All of the
specters I have encountered have been cavalry class, but I have spotted
a few brigade class threats as well. I even came across two warlord
class threats. Right, I should probably think about how to explain
monsters to the child...</em></p>
<p>"Monsters, including specters, follow the threat system created by
the Imperial Order, commonly referred to as the guild. The rankings of
the system were originally used to determine what kind of manpower was
needed to subdue the threat, but it has since been changed after the
guild became an independent party. Wanted individuals are also listed on
this scale, which is as follows:</p>
<p>Rogue Class, adversaries that likely need only one skilled individual
to subdue them. This class is commonly used to label everyday felons,
and is rarely used to describe monsters or specters.</p>
<p>Cadre Class, adversaries that require multiple people to subdue. For
more powerful felons, and a few monsters, this is the threat level you
would expect.</p>
<p>Battalion Class, which requires a uniform and orderly group to
subdue, with a large emphasis on orderly. Synergy is almost a
requirement to subdue such threats.</p>
<p>Cavalry Class, threats that require powerful arms or equipment to
defeat. Most monsters that have tough defenses will be of this class or
higher, and the felons of this threat are more likely to be named
criminals.</p>
<p>Brigade Class, threats that would need a large army to subdue. These
are the monsters that threaten to wipe out communities, and are often
being searched by the guild to defeat quickly.</p>
<p>Warlord Class, these beings require people like Master Darus, or even
Lord Cassius to subdue. Uniting trained warriors would likely be
ineffective, so the guild enlists special operators to handle these
threats.</p>
<p>Emperor Class, where the decision to combat these threats must be
discussed with the leaders of the area they reside in. Threats like
these... it's unsurprising that they might end up creating war.</p>
<p>Judgement Class, entities that require immediate suppression and many
figures to subdue. For people that reach this threat level and above,
they are the world's most wanted and are held in one of the most heavily
guarded containment facilities. I... know one of these individuals.</p>
<p>Apocalypse Class, which is realistically the highest class. The name
speaks for itself, but these beings are nothing short of terrifying. The
Heralds of Death from <em>The Man at Peak's End</em> would likely all be
in this tier.</p>
<p>And lastly... Demise Class. There has only been one entity of this
class, who started an entire era. You may have heard of them from the
story <em>The Four Heroes,</em> Alfa Lucius. This one individual
destroyed an entire portion of the Imperial continent, breaking it a
part and resulting in The Ruined Lands. Ah, I have been lost in thought
for too long, it seems that twenty minutes have passed."</p>
<p><em>There were exactly two warlord class threats, only two. This kind
of trial really is starting to feel like a death sentence, but not just
yet for me. And there's still the matter with what Lady Alice said
regarding our prerequisites, it makes this trial seem a lot more...
suspicious. A hundred specters being valued less than the heads of ten
Aesir seems so unbelievable now that I see what beasts they have for us.
I must be onto something... just what is honor and glory?</em></p>
<p><em>Groups seem to form no more than four. The amount of trust in one
another has weakened thanks to Lady Alice's words, but it surprises me
that there is still enough to form teams... but perhaps it's merely a
setup? Camaraderie, betrayal, how do these play into honor and glory?
There are many death traps all around, things are getting intense very
quickly. Am I the only one still pondering the meaning of this all? Was
I meant to get drunk on fear or thrill?</em></p>
<p>A man walked past the tree Walter had situated himself in,
overhearing his demo. <em>I guess a group this large would have its fair
share of strange individuals,</em> he thought to himself before carrying
on.</p>
<p><em>TIME TO BATTLE: 1:04:37</em></p>
<p><em>There really are only cavalry class specters or higher here, and
to make matters worse... a few of us have gone to challenge Cassius.
Perhaps they believed the courage to face such a man was the answer, but
I could sense their presence vanish one after another. After scouting
around, I found the locations of each of the captains. At first, I knew
Kevin was further west, deep in the forest, and Darus was out in the
open in the plains. I then encountered Babel, who was by the river
south-east, it seems that he refuses to take on groups and is planning
for one-on-one situations. The same cannot be said for Theros, who took
the high grounds. Theros specializes in ranged combat, if I were to
challenge one of the captains it would definitely not be him. After
returning to my original position, I've found that the captains will not
leave their positions; would they not give chase, either? Though, if
honor was considered, perhaps it wouldn't be right to run from the
battle in the first place.</em></p>
<p><em>TIME TO BATTLE: 0:07:27</em></p>
<p><em>I noticed something, or rather, I came to a revelation after
remembering what happened at Cathedral Hall. Though their heads were
taken, Cassius required the identification even though their heads would
have been enough. It seems the captains are preparing for battle, I
should make do with the information I have. But first, I need to check
if I am prepared for this trial.</em></p>
<p><em>My primary sword, always sheathed. I won't be needing this, not
soon at least. I have twenty knives on my person, and two spare dirks. I
have six antidotes in case I get poisoned, and two quality fabrics to
stop any lethal wound from bleeding. My chainmail has been strengthened
under this gear of mine, but just in case... I'll fortify this cloak so
it can act as a shield. With my abilities, each of these knives should
be enough to pierce through any armor. I have made my decision: the
"head" of an Aesir is worth more than a hundred specter, which is why we
must not cut down one another. Proof of victory is all that we need to
give.</em></p>
<p><em>If my internal clock is correct, the grace period should be
concluding soon.</em></p>
<p><em>In about...</em></p>
<p><em>3...</em></p>
<p><em>2...</em></p>
<p><em>1...</em></p>
<p><em>...</em></p>
<p>"The grace period has concluded." Lord Michael's voice thundered
through the silence.</p></content>
        <category term='	chapter'/>
    </entry>

  </feed>
